[
    {
      "question": "学校",
      "answer": "がっこう"
    },
    {
    "question": "川",
    "answer": "かわ"
    },
    {
    "question": "手",
    "answer": "て"
    },
    {
    "question": "戸",
    "answer": "と"
    },
    {
    "question": "眼鏡",
    "answer": "めがね"
    },
    {
        "question": "煙草",
        "answer": "たばこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "赤",
        "answer": "あか"
    },
    {
        "question": "仕事",
        "answer": "しごと"
    },
    {
    "question": "英語",
    "answer": "えいご"
    },
    {
        "question": "問題",
        "answer": "もんだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "部屋",
        "answer": "へや"
    },
    {
        "question": "子供",
        "answer": "こども"
    },
    {
        "question": "雨",
        "answer": "あめ"
    },
    {
    "question": "先生",
    "answer": "せんせい"
    },
    {
    "question": "年",
    "answer": "とし"
    },
    {
    "question": "手紙",
    "answer": "てがみ"
    },
    {
    "question": "電話",
    "answer": "でんわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "水",
        "answer": "みず"
    },
    {
        "question": "病気",
        "answer": "びょうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "上げる",
        "answer": "あげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "結婚",
        "answer": "けっこん"
    },
    {
    "question": "言葉",
    "answer": "ことば"
    },
    {
    "question": "目",
    "answer": "め"
    },
    {
    "question": "走る",
    "answer": "はしる"
    },
    {
        "question": "名前",
        "answer": "なまえ"
      },
  {
      "question": "旅行",
      "answer": "りょこう"
      },
      {
      "question": "道",
      "answer": "みち"
      },
      {
      "question": "飛行機",
      "answer": "ひこうき"
      },
      {
      "question": "映画",
      "answer": "えいが"
      },
      {
          "question": "音楽",
          "answer": "おんがく"
      },
      {
          "question": "木",
          "answer": "き"
      },
      {
          "question": "大学",
          "answer": "だいがく"
      },
      {
      "question": "時計",
      "answer": "とけい"
      },
      {
          "question": "家族",
          "answer": "かぞく"
      },
      {
          "question": "花",
          "answer": "はな"
      },
      {
          "question": "猫",
          "answer": "ねこ"
      },
      {
          "question": "毎日",
          "answer": "まいにち"
      },
      {
      "question": "宿題",
      "answer": "しゅくだい"
      },
      {
      "question": "雪",
      "answer": "ゆき"
      },
      {
      "question": "山",
      "answer": "やま"
      },
      {
      "question": "窓",
      "answer": "まど"
      },
      {
          "question": "動物",
          "answer": "どうぶつ"
      },
      {
          "question": "夜",
          "answer": "よる"
      },
      {
          "question": "料理",
          "answer": "りょうり"
      },
      {
          "question": "夏",
          "answer": "なつ"
      },
      {
      "question": "新聞",
      "answer": "しんぶん"
      },
      {
      "question": "公園",
      "answer": "こうえん"
      },
      {
      "question": "意味",
      "answer": "いみ"
      },
      {
        "question": "自転車",
        "answer": "じてんしゃ"
      },
  {
      "question": "足",
      "answer": "あし"
      },
      {
      "question": "電車",
      "answer": "でんしゃ"
      },
      {
      "question": "散歩",
      "answer": "さんぽ"
      },
      {
      "question": "声",
      "answer": "こえ"
      },
      {
          "question": "朝",
          "answer": "あさ"
      },
      {
          "question": "歌",
          "answer": "うた"
      },
      {
          "question": "靴",
          "answer": "くつ"
      },
      {
      "question": "箱",
      "answer": "はこ"
      },
      {
          "question": "机",
          "answer": "つくえ"
      },
      {
          "question": "帽子",
          "answer": "ぼうし"
      },
      {
          "question": "海",
          "answer": "うみ"
      },
      {
          "question": "授業",
          "answer": "じゅぎょう"
      },
      {
      "question": "銀行",
      "answer": "ぎんこう"
      },
      {
      "question": "写真",
      "answer": "しゃしん"
      },
      {
      "question": "冬",
      "answer": "ふゆ"
      },
      {
      "question": "村",
      "answer": "むら"
      },
      {
          "question": "傘",
          "answer": "かさ"
      },
      {
          "question": "口",
          "answer": "くち"
      },
      {
          "question": "橋",
          "answer": "はし"
      },
      {
          "question": "病院",
          "answer": "びょういん"
      },
      {
      "question": "図書館",
      "answer": "としょかん"
      },
      {
      "question": "春",
      "answer": "はる"
      },
      {
      "question": "買い物",
      "answer": "かいもの"
      },
      {
        "question": "椅子",
        "answer": "いす"
      },
  {
      "question": "自動車",
      "answer": "じどうしゃ"
      },
      {
      "question": "色",
      "answer": "いろ"
      },
      {
      "question": "卵",
      "answer": "たまご"
      },
      {
        "question": "肉",
        "answer": "にく"
        },
        {
        "question": "風邪",
        "answer": "かぜ"
        },
        {
        "question": "掃除",
        "answer": "そうじ"
        },
        {
        "question": "紙",
        "answer": "かみ"
        },
        {
        "question": "鍵",
        "answer": "かぎ"
        },
        {
        "question": "雑誌",
        "answer": "ざっし"
        },
        {
        "question": "切符",
        "answer": "きっぷ"
        },
        {
        "question": "外国人",
        "answer": "がいこくじん"
        },
        {
        "question": "財布",
        "answer": "さいふ"
        },
        {
        "question": "鉛筆",
        "answer": "えんぴつ"
        },
        {
        "question": "大人",
        "answer": "おとな"
        },
        {
        "question": "塩",
        "answer": "しお"
        },
        {
        "question": "地図",
        "answer": "ちず"
        },
        {
        "question": "砂糖",
        "answer": "さとう"
        },
        {
        "question": "夏休み",
        "answer": "なつやすみ"
        },
        {
        "question": "池",
        "answer": "いけ"
        },
        {
        "question": "郵便局",
        "answer": "ゆうびんきょく"
        },
        {
        "question": "教室",
        "answer": "きょうしつ"
        },
        {
        "question": "耳",
        "answer": "みみ"
        },
        {
        "question": "切手",
        "answer": "きって"
        },
        {
        "question": "台所",
        "answer": "だいどころ"
        },
        {
        "question": "電気",
        "answer": "でんき"
        },
        {
        "question": "作文",
        "answer": "さくぶん"
        },
        {
            "question": "作文",
            "answer": "さくぶん"
            },
            {
            "question": "紅茶",
            "answer": "こうちゃ"
            },
            {
            "question": "家庭",
            "answer": "かてい"
            },
            {
            "question": "野菜",
            "answer": "やさい"
            },
            {
            "question": "風呂",
            "answer": "ふろ"
            },
            {
            "question": "玄関",
            "answer": "げんかん"
            },
            {
            "question": "地下鉄",
            "answer": "ちかてつ"
            },
            {
            "question": "鼻",
            "answer": "はな"
            },
            {
            "question": "緑",
            "answer": "みどり"
            },
            {
            "question": "昼",
            "answer": "ひる"
            },
            {
            "question": "西",
            "answer": "にし"
            },
            {
            "question": "白",
            "answer": "しろ"
            },
            {
            "question": "洗濯",
            "answer": "せんたく"
            },
            {
            "question": "冷蔵庫",
            "answer": "れいぞうこ"
            },
            {
            "question": "南",
            "answer": "みなみ"
            },
            {
            "question": "火曜日",
            "answer": "かようび"
            },
            {
            "question": "北",
            "answer": "きた"
            },
            {
            "question": "茶色",
            "answer": "ちゃいろ"
            },
            {
            "question": "黒",
            "answer": "くろ"
            },
            {
            "question": "喫茶店",
            "answer": "きっさてん"
            },
            {
                "question": "青",
                "answer": "あお"
                },
                {
                "question": "靴下",
                "answer": "くつした"
                },
                {
                "question": "封筒",
                "answer": "ふうとう"
                },
                {
                "question": "辺",
                "answer": "へん"
                },
                {
                "question": "黄色",
                "answer": "きいろ"
                },
                {
                "question": "映画館",
                "answer": "えいがかん"
                },
                {
                "question": "箸",
                "answer": "はし"
                },
                {
                "question": "食堂",
                "answer": "しょくどう"
                },
                {
                "question": "牛肉",
                "answer": "ぎゅうにく"
                },
                {
                "question": "交差点",
                "answer": "こうさてん"
                },
                {
                "question": "漢字",
                "answer": "かんじ"
                },
                {
                "question": "茶わん",
                "answer": "ちゃわん"
                },
                {
                "question": "曇り",
                "answer": "くもり"
                },
                {
                "question": "背広",
                "answer": "せびろ"
                },
                {
                "question": "灰皿",
                "answer": "はいざら"
                },
                {
                "question": "万年筆",
                "answer": "まんねんひつ"
                },
                {
                "question": "大使館",
                "answer": "たいしかん"
                },
                {
                "question": "交番",
                "answer": "こうばん"
                },
                {
                "question": "豚肉",
                "answer": "ぶたにく"
                },
                {
                "question": "飲む",
                "answer": "のむ"
                },
                {
                    "question": "頭-1",
                    "answer": "あたま"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "日曜日",
                    "answer": "にちようび"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "誕生日",
                    "answer": "たんじょうび"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "可愛い",
                    "answer": "かわいい"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "鞄",
                    "answer": "かばん"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "土曜日",
                    "answer": "どようび"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "月曜日",
                    "answer": "げつようび"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "金曜日",
                    "answer": "きんようび"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "花瓶",
                    "answer": "かびん"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "木曜日",
                    "answer": "もくようび"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "本棚",
                    "answer": "ほんだな"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "石鹸",
                    "answer": "せっけん"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "水曜日",
                    "answer": "すいようび"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "飴",
                    "answer": "あめ"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "八百屋",
                    "answer": "やおや"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "成る",
                    "answer": "なる"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "より",
                    "answer": "より"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "一番",
                    "answer": "いちばん"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "私",
                    "answer": "わたし"
                    },
                    {
                    "question": "外",
                    "answer": "そと"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "姉",
                        "answer": "あね"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "百",
                        "answer": "ひゃく"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "在る",
                        "answer": "ある"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "其の",
                        "answer": "その"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "言う",
                        "answer": "いう"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "出来る",
                        "answer": "できる"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "良い",
                        "answer": "よい"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "下さい",
                        "answer": "ください"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "見る",
                        "answer": "みる"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "此の",
                        "answer": "この"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "自分",
                        "answer": "じぶん"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "知る",
                        "answer": "しる"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "持つ",
                        "answer": "もつ"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "何",
                        "answer": "なに"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "車",
                        "answer": "くるま"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "話す",
                        "answer": "はなす"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "今",
                        "answer": "いま"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "今日",
                        "answer": "きょう"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "買う",
                        "answer": "かう"
                        },
                        {
                        "question": "読む",
                        "answer": "よむ"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "皆",
                            "answer": "みんな"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "新しい",
                            "answer": "あたらしい"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "話",
                            "answer": "はなし"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "明日",
                            "answer": "あした"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "昨日",
                            "answer": "きのう"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "出る",
                            "answer": "でる"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "勉強",
                            "answer": "べんきょう"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "取る",
                            "answer": "とる"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "誰",
                            "answer": "だれ"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "お金",
                            "answer": "おかね"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "男",
                            "answer": "おとこ"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "犬",
                            "answer": "いぬ"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "使う",
                            "answer": "つかう"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "大変",
                            "answer": "たいへん"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "待つ",
                            "answer": "まつ"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "作る",
                            "answer": "つくる"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "後ろ",
                            "answer": "うしろ"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "町",
                            "answer": "まち"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "駅",
                            "answer": "えき"
                            },
                            {
                            "question": "少し",
                            "answer": "すこし"
                            },
                            {
                                "question": "貴方-1",
                                "answer": "あなた"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "欲しい",
                                "answer": "ほしい"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "行く",
                                "answer": "いく"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "乗る",
                                "answer": "のる"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "大きな",
                                "answer": "おおきな"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "医者",
                                "answer": "いしゃ"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "終わる",
                                "answer": "おわる"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "学生",
                                "answer": "がくせい"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "長い",
                                "answer": "ながい"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "何の",
                                "answer": "どの"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "国",
                                "answer": "くに"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "又",
                                "answer": "また"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "高い",
                                "answer": "たかい"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "余り",
                                "answer": "あまり"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "難しい",
                                "answer": "むずかしい"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "友達",
                                "answer": "ともだち"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "本当",
                                "answer": "ほんとう"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "一つ",
                                "answer": "ひとつ"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "寝る",
                                "answer": "ねる"
                                },
                                {
                                "question": "生徒",
                                "answer": "せいと"
                                },
                                {
                                    "question": "忙しい",
                                    "answer": "いそがしい"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "両親",
                                    "answer": "りょうしん"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "泳ぐ",
                                    "answer": "およぐ"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "出す",
                                    "answer": "だす"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "立つ",
                                    "answer": "たつ"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "早い",
                                    "answer": "はやい"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "楽しい",
                                    "answer": "たのしい"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "面白い",
                                    "answer": "おもしろい"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "絵",
                                    "answer": "え"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "女の子",
                                    "answer": "おんなのこ"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "着る",
                                    "answer": "きる"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "上手",
                                    "answer": "じょうず"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "古い",
                                    "answer": "ふるい"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "強い",
                                    "answer": "つよい"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "全部",
                                    "answer": "ぜんぶ"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "呼ぶ",
                                    "answer": "よぶ"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "午後",
                                    "answer": "ごご"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "掛ける",
                                    "answer": "かける"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "辞書",
                                    "answer": "じしょ"
                                    },
                                    {
                                    "question": "天気",
                                    "answer": "てんき"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "question": "体",
                                        "answer": "からだ"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "大きい",
                                        "answer": "おおきい"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "質問",
                                        "answer": "しつもん"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "夕べ",
                                        "answer": "ゆうべ"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "有名",
                                        "answer": "ゆうめい"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "兄",
                                        "answer": "あに"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "歌う",
                                        "answer": "うたう"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "上る",
                                        "answer": "のぼる"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "鳥",
                                        "answer": "とり"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "服",
                                        "answer": "ふく"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "時々",
                                        "answer": "ときどき"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "妹",
                                        "answer": "いもうと"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "二つ",
                                        "answer": "ふたつ"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "頼む",
                                        "answer": "たのむ"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "今朝",
                                        "answer": "けさ"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "お父さん",
                                        "answer": "おとうさん"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "遅い",
                                        "answer": "おそい"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "借りる",
                                        "answer": "かりる"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "薬",
                                        "answer": "くすり"
                                        },
                                        {
                                        "question": "庭",
                                        "answer": "にわ"
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "question": "外国",
                                            "answer": "がいこく"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "小さい",
                                            "answer": "ちいさい"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "元気",
                                            "answer": "げんき"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "弟",
                                            "answer": "おとうと"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "魚",
                                            "answer": "さかな"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "今年",
                                            "answer": "ことし"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "お母さん",
                                            "answer": "おかあさん"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "男の子",
                                            "answer": "おとこのこ"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "飛ぶ",
                                            "answer": "とぶ"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "売る",
                                            "answer": "うる"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "静か",
                                            "answer": "しずか"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "休む",
                                            "answer": "やすむ"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "食べ物",
                                            "answer": "たべもの"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "大切",
                                            "answer": "たいせつ"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "来週",
                                            "answer": "らいしゅう"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "警官",
                                            "answer": "けいかん"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "建物",
                                            "answer": "たてもの"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "暖かい",
                                            "answer": "あたたかい"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "降りる",
                                            "answer": "おりる"
                                            },
                                            {
                                            "question": "止まる",
                                            "answer": "とまる"
                                            },
                                            {
                                                "question": "一緒",
                                                "answer": "いっしょ"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "先週",
                                                "answer": "せんしゅう"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "白い",
                                                "answer": "しろい"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "二",
                                                "answer": "に"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "少ない",
                                                "answer": "すくない"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "赤い",
                                                "answer": "あかい"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "洗う",
                                                "answer": "あらう"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "嫌い",
                                                "answer": "きらい"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "立派",
                                                "answer": "りっぱ"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "暇",
                                                "answer": "ひま"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "お茶",
                                                "answer": "おちゃ"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "広い",
                                                "answer": "ひろい"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "去年",
                                                "answer": "きょねん"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "大好き",
                                                "answer": "だいすき"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "隣",
                                                "answer": "となり"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "女",
                                                "answer": "おんな"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "多分",
                                                "answer": "たぶん"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "切る",
                                                "answer": "きる"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "嫌",
                                                "answer": "いや"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                "question": "毎朝",
                                                "answer": "まいあさ"
                                                },
                                                {
                                                    "question": "荷物",
                                                    "answer": "にもつ"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "番号",
                                                    "answer": "ばんごう"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "返す",
                                                    "answer": "かえす"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "来年",
                                                    "answer": "らいねん"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "明るい",
                                                    "answer": "あかるい"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "近い",
                                                    "answer": "ちかい"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "向こう",
                                                    "answer": "むこう"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "始め",
                                                    "answer": "はじめ"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "痛い",
                                                    "answer": "いたい"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "休み",
                                                    "answer": "やすみ"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "練習",
                                                    "answer": "れんしゅう"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "十",
                                                    "answer": "じゅう"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "上着",
                                                    "answer": "うわぎ"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "先月",
                                                    "answer": "せんげつ"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "結構",
                                                    "answer": "けっこう"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "毎年",
                                                    "answer": "まいとし"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "兄弟",
                                                    "answer": "きょうだい"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "来月",
                                                    "answer": "らいげつ"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "五",
                                                    "answer": "ご"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                    "question": "飲み物",
                                                    "answer": "のみもの"
                                                    },
                                                    {
                                                        "question": "弱い",
                                                        "answer": "よわい"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "牛乳",
                                                        "answer": "ぎゅうにゅう"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "三",
                                                        "answer": "さん"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "大丈夫",
                                                        "answer": "だいじょうぶ"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "黒い",
                                                        "answer": "くろい"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "皆さん",
                                                        "answer": "みなさん"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "半分",
                                                        "answer": "はんぶん"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "押す",
                                                        "answer": "おす"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "勤める",
                                                        "answer": "つとめる"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "熱い",
                                                        "answer": "あつい"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "三つ",
                                                        "answer": "みっつ"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "果物",
                                                        "answer": "くだもの"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "今週",
                                                        "answer": "こんしゅう"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "右",
                                                        "answer": "みぎ"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "甘い",
                                                        "answer": "あまい"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "晩",
                                                        "answer": "ばん"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "幾つ",
                                                        "answer": "いくつ"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "階段",
                                                        "answer": "かいだん"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "大勢",
                                                        "answer": "おおぜい"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                        "question": "張る",
                                                        "answer": "はる"
                                                        },
                                                        {
                                                            "question": "夕方",
                                                            "answer": "ゆうがた"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "低い",
                                                            "answer": "ひくい"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "左",
                                                            "answer": "ひだり"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "毎週",
                                                            "answer": "まいしゅう"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "下手",
                                                            "answer": "へた"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "千",
                                                            "answer": "せん"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "渡す",
                                                            "answer": "わたす"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "午前",
                                                            "answer": "ごぜん"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "丸い",
                                                            "answer": "まるい"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "便利",
                                                            "answer": "べんり"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "今月",
                                                            "answer": "こんげつ"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "浴びる",
                                                            "answer": "あびる"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "半",
                                                            "answer": "はん"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "洋服",
                                                            "answer": "ようふく"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "撮る",
                                                            "answer": "とる"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "締める",
                                                            "answer": "しめる"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "文章",
                                                            "answer": "ぶんしょう"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "薄い",
                                                            "answer": "うすい"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "八",
                                                            "answer": "はち"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                            "question": "横",
                                                            "answer": "よこ"
                                                            },
                                                            {
                                                                "question": "六",
                                                                "answer": "ろく"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "四つ",
                                                                "answer": "よっつ"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "丈夫",
                                                                "answer": "じょうぶ"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "毎晩",
                                                                "answer": "まいばん"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "東",
                                                                "answer": "ひがし"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "五つ",
                                                                "answer": "いつつ"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "晴れ",
                                                                "answer": "はれ"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "細い",
                                                                "answer": "ほそい"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "廊下",
                                                                "answer": "ろうか"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "太い",
                                                                "answer": "ふとい"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "縦",
                                                                "answer": "たて"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "七つ",
                                                                "answer": "ななつ"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "九つ",
                                                                "answer": "ここのつ"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "留学生",
                                                                "answer": "りゅうがくせい"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "一昨年",
                                                                "answer": "おととし"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "人",
                                                                "answer": "ひと"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "居る",
                                                                "answer": "いる"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "其れ",
                                                                "answer": "それ"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "物",
                                                                "answer": "もの"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                "question": "家",
                                                                "answer": "いえ"
                                                                },
                                                                {
                                                                    "question": "本",
                                                                    "answer": "ほん"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "迚も",
                                                                    "answer": "とても"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "会う",
                                                                    "answer": "あう"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "好き",
                                                                    "answer": "すき"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "分かる",
                                                                    "answer": "わかる"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "此れ",
                                                                    "answer": "これ"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "聞く",
                                                                    "answer": "きく"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "所",
                                                                    "answer": "ところ"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "先",
                                                                    "answer": "さき"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "何時も",
                                                                    "answer": "いつも"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "書く",
                                                                    "answer": "かく"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "沢山",
                                                                    "answer": "たくさん"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "入る",
                                                                    "answer": "はいる"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "置く",
                                                                    "answer": "おく"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "何処",
                                                                    "answer": "どこ"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "住む",
                                                                    "answer": "すむ"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "食べる",
                                                                    "answer": "たべる"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "歩く",
                                                                    "answer": "あるく"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "働く",
                                                                    "answer": "はたらく"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                    "question": "着く",
                                                                    "answer": "つく"
                                                                    },
                                                                    {
                                                                        "question": "上",
                                                                        "answer": "うえ"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "悪い",
                                                                        "answer": "わるい"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "教える",
                                                                        "answer": "おしえる"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "降る",
                                                                        "answer": "ふる"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "死ぬ",
                                                                        "answer": "しぬ"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "帰る",
                                                                        "answer": "かえる"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "忘れる",
                                                                        "answer": "わすれる"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "多い",
                                                                        "answer": "おおい"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "出掛ける",
                                                                        "answer": "でかける"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "若い",
                                                                        "answer": "わかい"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "掛かる",
                                                                        "answer": "かかる"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "同じ",
                                                                        "answer": "おなじ"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "起きる",
                                                                        "answer": "おきる"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "座る",
                                                                        "answer": "すわる"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "店",
                                                                        "answer": "みせ"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "入れる",
                                                                        "answer": "いれる"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "何方",
                                                                        "answer": "どなた"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "一寸",
                                                                        "answer": "ちょっと"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "疲れる",
                                                                        "answer": "つかれる"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                        "question": "開ける",
                                                                        "answer": "あける"
                                                                        },
                                                                        {
                                                                            "question": "何故",
                                                                            "answer": "なぜ"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "一日",
                                                                            "answer": "いちにち"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "寒い",
                                                                            "answer": "さむい"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "見せる",
                                                                            "answer": "みせる"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "違う",
                                                                            "answer": "ちがう"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "如何して",
                                                                            "answer": "どうして"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "付ける",
                                                                            "answer": "つける"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "覚える",
                                                                            "answer": "おぼえる"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "近く",
                                                                            "answer": "ちかく"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "風",
                                                                            "answer": "かぜ"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "困る",
                                                                            "answer": "こまる"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "生まれる",
                                                                            "answer": "うまれる"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "丁度",
                                                                            "answer": "ちょうど"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "初めて",
                                                                            "answer": "はじめて"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "始まる",
                                                                            "answer": "はじまる"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "貸す",
                                                                            "answer": "かす"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "奇麗",
                                                                            "answer": "きれい"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "幾ら",
                                                                            "answer": "いくら"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "空",
                                                                            "answer": "そら"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                            "question": "弾く",
                                                                            "answer": "ひく"
                                                                            },
                                                                            {
                                                                                "question": "暑い",
                                                                                "answer": "あつい"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "遊ぶ",
                                                                                "answer": "あそぶ"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "然し",
                                                                                "answer": "しかし"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "無くす",
                                                                                "answer": "なくす"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "色々",
                                                                                "answer": "いろいろ"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "渡る",
                                                                                "answer": "わたる"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "暗い",
                                                                                "answer": "くらい"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "此方",
                                                                                "answer": "こちら"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "重い",
                                                                                "answer": "おもい"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "今晩",
                                                                                "answer": "こんばん"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "美味しい",
                                                                                "answer": "おいしい"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "消す",
                                                                                "answer": "けす"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "易しい",
                                                                                "answer": "やさしい"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "閉める",
                                                                                "answer": "しめる"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "安い",
                                                                                "answer": "やすい"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "遠い",
                                                                                "answer": "とおい"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "短い",
                                                                                "answer": "みじかい"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "晴れる",
                                                                                "answer": "はれる"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "曲がる",
                                                                                "answer": "まがる"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                "question": "消える",
                                                                                "answer": "きえる"
                                                                                },
                                                                                {
                                                                                    "question": "冷たい",
                                                                                    "answer": "つめたい"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "青い",
                                                                                    "answer": "あおい"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "吹く",
                                                                                    "answer": "ふく"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "頁",
                                                                                    "answer": "ページ"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "奥さん",
                                                                                    "answer": "おくさん"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "引く",
                                                                                    "answer": "ひく"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "段々",
                                                                                    "answer": "だんだん"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "習う",
                                                                                    "answer": "ならう"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "彼処",
                                                                                    "answer": "あそこ"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "狭い",
                                                                                    "answer": "せまい"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "軽い",
                                                                                    "answer": "かるい"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "脱ぐ",
                                                                                    "answer": "ぬぐ"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "万",
                                                                                    "answer": "まん"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "煩い",
                                                                                    "answer": "うるさい"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "並ぶ",
                                                                                    "answer": "ならぶ"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "吸う",
                                                                                    "answer": "すう"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "詰らない",
                                                                                    "answer": "つまらない"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "閉まる",
                                                                                    "answer": "しまる"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "咲く",
                                                                                    "answer": "さく"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                    "question": "真っ直ぐ",
                                                                                    "answer": "まっすぐ"
                                                                                    },
                                                                                    {
                                                                                        "question": "一",
                                                                                        "answer": "いち"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "お祖母さん",
                                                                                        "answer": "おばあさん"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "涼しい",
                                                                                        "answer": "すずしい"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "其方",
                                                                                        "answer": "そちら"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "厚い",
                                                                                        "answer": "あつい"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "お兄さん",
                                                                                        "answer": "おにいさん"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "お姉さん",
                                                                                        "answer": "おねえさん"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "汚い",
                                                                                        "answer": "きたない"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "危ない",
                                                                                        "answer": "あぶない"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "並べる",
                                                                                        "answer": "ならべる"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "お腹",
                                                                                        "answer": "おなか"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "不味い",
                                                                                        "answer": "まずい"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "曇る",
                                                                                        "answer": "くもる"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "ご飯",
                                                                                        "answer": "ごはん"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "黄色い",
                                                                                        "answer": "きいろい"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "お菓子",
                                                                                        "answer": "おかし"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "磨く",
                                                                                        "answer": "みがく"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "賑やか",
                                                                                        "answer": "にぎやか"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "鳴く",
                                                                                        "answer": "なく"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                        "question": "夕飯",
                                                                                        "answer": "ゆうはん"
                                                                                        },
                                                                                        {
                                                                                            "question": "葉書",
                                                                                            "answer": "はがき"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "朝ご飯",
                                                                                            "answer": "あさごはん"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "六つ",
                                                                                            "answer": "むっつ"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "お手洗い",
                                                                                            "answer": "おてあらい"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "お巡りさん",
                                                                                            "answer": "おまわりさん"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "差す",
                                                                                            "answer": "さす"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "零",
                                                                                            "answer": "れい"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "二十日",
                                                                                            "answer": "はつか"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "粁",
                                                                                            "answer": "キロメートル"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "八つ",
                                                                                            "answer": "やっつ"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "再来年",
                                                                                            "answer": "さらいねん"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "燐寸",
                                                                                            "answer": "マッチ"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "良く",
                                                                                            "answer": "よく"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "其処",
                                                                                            "answer": "そこ"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "小さな",
                                                                                            "answer": "ちいさな"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "答える",
                                                                                            "answer": "こたえる"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "もう一度",
                                                                                            "answer": "もういちど"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "要る",
                                                                                            "answer": "いる"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                            "question": "背",
                                                                                            "answer": "せ"
                                                                                            },
                                                                                            {
                                                                                                "question": "お弁当",
                                                                                                "answer": "おべんとう"
                                                                                                },
                                                                                                {
                                                                                                "question": "晩御飯",
                                                                                                "answer": "ばんごはん"
                                                                                                },
                                                                                                {
                                                                                                "question": "昼ご飯",
                                                                                                "answer": "ひるごはん"
                                                                                                },
                                                                                                {
                                                                                                "question": "等",
                                                                                                "answer": "など"
                                                                                                },
                                                                                                {
                                                                                                "question": "中",
                                                                                                "answer": "なか"
                                                                                                },
                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                    "question": "米",
                                                                                                    "answer": "メートル"
                                                                                                    },
                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                        "question": "一昨日",
                                                                                                        "answer": "おととい"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "醤油",
                                                                                                        "answer": "しょうゆ"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "はい",
                                                                                                        "answer": "はい"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "為る",
                                                                                                        "answer": "する"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "彼",
                                                                                                        "answer": "あれ"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "一日",
                                                                                                        "answer": "ついたち"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "三日",
                                                                                                        "answer": "みっか"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "二日",
                                                                                                        "answer": "ふつか"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "五日",
                                                                                                        "answer": "いつか"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "十日",
                                                                                                        "answer": "とおか"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "六日",
                                                                                                        "answer": "むいか"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                        "question": "八日",
                                                                                                        "answer": "ようか"
                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                            "question": "九日",
                                                                                                            "answer": "ここのか"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "来る",
                                                                                                            "answer": "くる"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "後",
                                                                                                            "answer": "あと"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "会社",
                                                                                                            "answer": "かいしゃ"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "一人",
                                                                                                            "answer": "ひとり"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "二人",
                                                                                                            "answer": "ふたり"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "側",
                                                                                                            "answer": "そば"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "否",
                                                                                                            "answer": "いいえ"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "辛い",
                                                                                                            "answer": "からい"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "門",
                                                                                                            "answer": "もん"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "角",
                                                                                                            "answer": "かど"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "毎月",
                                                                                                            "answer": "まいつき"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "七",
                                                                                                            "answer": "しち"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "伯母さん",
                                                                                                            "answer": "おばさん"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "四",
                                                                                                            "answer": "し"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "お風呂",
                                                                                                            "answer": "おふろ"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "お酒",
                                                                                                            "answer": "おさけ"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "入口",
                                                                                                            "answer": "いりぐち"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "出口",
                                                                                                            "answer": "でぐち"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                            "question": "お皿",
                                                                                                            "answer": "おさら"
                                                                                                            },
                                                                                                            {
                                                                                                                "question": "此処",
                                                                                                                "answer": "ここ"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "前",
                                                                                                                "answer": "まえ"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "如何",
                                                                                                                "answer": "どう"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "方",
                                                                                                                "answer": "かた"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "未だ",
                                                                                                                "answer": "まだ"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "何時",
                                                                                                                "answer": "いつ"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "他",
                                                                                                                "answer": "ほか"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "次",
                                                                                                                "answer": "つぎ"
                                                                                                                }, 
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "何方",
                                                                                                                "answer": "どちら"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "誰か",
                                                                                                                "answer": "だれか"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "開く",
                                                                                                                "answer": "あく"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "下",
                                                                                                                "answer": "した"
                                                                                                                },
                                                                                                                {
                                                                                                                "question": "然して",
                                                                                                                "answer": "そして"
                                                                                                                },  
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                    "question": "其れから",
                                                                                                                    "answer": "それから"
                                                                                                                    },  
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                    "question": "其れでは",
                                                                                                                    "answer": "それでは"
                                                                                                                    },
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                    "question": "明後日",
                                                                                                                    "answer": "あさって"
                                                                                                                    },
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                    "question": "何れ",
                                                                                                                    "answer": "どれ"
                                                                                                                    },
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                    "question": "二十歳",
                                                                                                                    "answer": "はたち"
                                                                                                                    },
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                    "question": "彼方",
                                                                                                                    "answer": "あちら"
                                                                                                                    },
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                    "question": "温い",
                                                                                                                    "answer": "ぬるい"
                                                                                                                    },
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                    "question": "四日",
                                                                                                                    "answer": "よっか"
                                                                                                                    },
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                    "question": "七日",
                                                                                                                    "answer": "なのか"
                                                                                                                    },
                                                                                                                    {
                                                                                                                        "question": "然うして",
                                                                                                                        "answer": "そうして"
                                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                                        "question": "瓦",
                                                                                                                        "answer": "グラム"
                                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                                        "question": "瓩",
                                                                                                                        "answer": "キログラム"
                                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                                        "question": "直ぐに",
                                                                                                                        "answer": "すぐに"
                                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                                        "question": "一月",
                                                                                                                        "answer": "ひとつき"
                                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                                        "question": "秋",
                                                                                                                        "answer": "あき"
                                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                                        "question": "字引",
                                                                                                                        "answer": "じびき"
                                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                                        "question": "咖哩",
                                                                                                                        "answer": "カレー"
                                                                                                                        },
                                                                                                                        {
                                                                                                                        "question": "三",
                                                                                                                        "answer": "サン"
                                                                                                                        }                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                              
  ]